[{"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 1], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 1], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 1], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 1], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 1], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/左手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 1], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 0], [3, 1]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手3.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 1], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "连一连", "content": [[{"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手1.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/组件/认识左右/1-5-3-06/右手2.svg", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "左手", "type": "text"}, {"val": "右手", "type": "text"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-connect"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 1], [2, 1], [3, 0]], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-06"}]